[

](https://spacial.com/)



* Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
==============

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this policy in order for you to understand how we  
collect, use, communicate and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.

When accessing the https://spacial.com website, Spacial Audio will learn certain information  
about you during your visit.

Similar to other commercial websites, our website utilizes a standard [technology](https://www.brreplicasderelogios.com.br/) called ‘cookies’ (see explanation  
below) and server logs to collect information about how our site is used. Information gathered through cookies and  
server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our site, and the websites visited  
just before and just after our own, as well as your IP address.

#### Use of Cookies

A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a website,  
that site’s computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically  
designated for cookies. Each website can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser’s preferences allow it, but  
(to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a website  
to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites.

#### IP Addresses

IP addresses are used by your computer every time you are connected to the Internet. Your IP address is a number that is  
used by computers on the network to identify your computer. IP addresses are automatically collected by our web server  
as part of demographic and profile data known as “traffic data” so that data (such as the Web pages you request) can be  
sent to you.

#### Email Information

If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your  
email address and our responses. We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ in  
the maintenance of information received online, mail and telephone. This also applies when you register for our website,  
sign up through any of our forms using your email address  
or make a purchase on this site. For further information see the email policies below.

#### How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?

Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering our business activities, providing customer  
service and making available other items and services to our customers and prospective customers.

Spacial Audio will not obtain personally-identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to  
provide such information to us, nor will such information be sold or otherwise transferred to unaffiliated third parties  
without the approval of the user at the time of collection.

We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so, in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the  
law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights.

#### Email Policies

We are committed to keeping your e-mail address confidential. We do not [sell](https://www.noob.to/), rent, or lease our subscription lists to  
third parties, and we will not provide your personal information to any third party individual, government agency, or  
company at any time unless strictly compelled to do so by law.

We will use your e-mail address solely to provide timely information about Spacial Audio.

We will maintain the information you send via e-mail in accordance with applicable federal law.

#### CAN-SPAM Compliance

In compliance with the CAN-SPAM Act, all e-mail sent from our organization will clearly state who the e-mail is from and  
provide clear information on how to contact the sender. In addition, all e-mail messages will also contain concise  
information on how to remove yourself from our mailing list so that you receive no further e-mail communication from us.

#### Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners by reading the  
unsubscribe instructions located at the bottom of any e-mail they receive from us at anytime.

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials may opt-out of receiving these  
communications by clicking on the unsubscribe link in the e-mail.

#### Use of External Links

https://spacial.com may contain links to many other websites. Spacial Audio cannot guarantee the  
accuracy of information found at any linked site. Links to or from external sites not owned or controlled by Spacial  
Audio do not constitute an endorsement by Spacial Audio or any of its employees of the sponsors of these sites or the  
products or  
information presented therein.

By accessing this web site, you are agreeing to be bound by these web site Terms and Conditions of Use, all applicable  
laws and regulations, and agree that you are responsible for compliance with any applicable local laws. If you do not  
agree with any of these terms, you are prohibited from using or accessing this site. The materials contained in this web  
site are protected by applicable copyright and trade mark  
law.

#### Intellectual Property Rights

All copyrights, trademarks, patents and other intellectual property rights in and on our website and all content and  
software located on the site shall remain the sole property of Spacial Audio or its licensors. The use of our  
trademarks, content and intellectual property is forbidden without the express written consent from Spacial Audio.

#### You must not:

* Republish material from our website without prior written consent.
* Sell or rent material from our website.
* Reproduce, duplicate, create derivative, copy or otherwise exploit material on our website for any purpose.
* Redistribute any content from our website, including onto another website.

#### Acceptable Use

You agree to use our website only for lawful purposes, and in a way that does not infringe the rights of, restrict or  
inhibit anyone else’s use and enjoyment of the website. Prohibited behavior includes harassing or causing distress or  
inconvenience to any other user, transmitting obscene or offensive content or disrupting the normal flow of dialogue  
within our website.

You must not use our website to send unsolicited commercial communications. You must not use the content on our website  
for any marketing related purpose without our express written consent.

#### Restricted Access

We may in the future need to restrict access to parts (or all) of our website and reserve full rights to do so. If, at  
any point, we provide you with a username and password for you to access restricted areas of our website, you must  
ensure that both your username and password are kept confidential.

#### Use of Testimonials

In accordance to with the FTC guidelines concerning the use of endorsements and testimonials in advertising, please be  
aware of the following:

Testimonials that appear on this site are actually received via text, audio or video submission. They are individual  
experiences, reflecting real life experiences of those who have used our products and/or services in some way. They are  
individual results and results do vary. We do not claim that they are typical results. The testimonials are not  
necessarily representative of all of those who will use our products  
and/or services.

The testimonials displayed in any form on this site (text, audio, video or other) are reproduced verbatim, except for  
correction of grammatical or typing errors. Some may have been shortened. In other words, not the whole message received  
by the testimonial writer is displayed when it seems too lengthy or not the whole statement seems relevant for the  
general public.

Spacial Audio is not responsible for any of the opinions or comments posted on  
https://spacial.com. Spacial Audio is not a forum for testimonials, however provides testimonials  
as a means for customers to share their experiences with one another. To protect against abuse, all testimonials appear  
after they have been reviewed by management  
of Spacial Audio. Spacial Audio doe not share the opinions, views or commentary of any testimonials on  
https://spacial.com – the opinions are strictly the views of the testimonial source.

The testimonials are never intended to make claims that our products and/or services can be used to diagnose, treat,  
cure, mitigate or prevent any disease. Any such claims, implicit or explicit, in any shape or form, have not been  
clinically tested or evaluated.

#### How Do We Protect Your Information and Secure Information Transmissions?

Email is not recognized as a secure medium of communication. For this reason, we request that you do not send private  
information to us by email. However, doing so is allowed, but at your own risk. Some of the information you may enter on  
our website may be transmitted securely via a secure medium known as Secure Sockets Layer, or SSL. Credit Card  
information and other sensitive information is never transmitted  
via email.

Spacial Audio may use software programs to create summary statistics, which are used for such purposes as assessing the  
number of visitors to the different sections of our site, what information is of most and least interest, determining  
technical design specifications, and identifying system performance or problem areas.

For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, Spacial Audio uses software  
programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise  
cause damage.

#### Disclaimer and Limitation of Liability

Spacial Audio makes no representations, warranties, or assurances as to the accuracy, currency or completeness of the  
content contain on this website or any sites linked to this site.

All the materials on this site are provided ‘as is’ without any express or implied warranty of any kind, including  
warranties of merchantability, noninfringement of intellectual property or fitness for any particular purpose. In no  
event shall Spacial Audio or its agents or associates be liable for any damages whatsoever (including, without  
limitation, damages for loss of profits, business  
interruption, loss of information, injury or death) arising out of the use of or inability to use the materials, even if  
Spacial Audio has been advised of the possibility of such loss or damages.

#### Policy Changes

We reserve the right to amend this privacy policy at any time with or without notice. However, please be assured that if  
the privacy policy changes in the future, we will not use the personal information you have submitted to us under this  
privacy policy in a manner that is materially inconsistent with this privacy policy, without your prior consent.

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the  
confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.

#### The Personal Information We Collect

You may visit our Site without providing any of your personal information to us. At this time, the only personal information that we collect through our Site is personal information that you voluntarily provide to us when you sign up for a free trial or SAM Broadcaster Cloud service.

We may also automatically collect general anonymous information related to your use of our Site, such as the date and time you visit the Site and the pages you visit on the Site. Our servers may also automatically collect information about the type of browser you use and the name of your Internet Service Provider. In addition, we may collect “cookie” information from your browser to identify your computer and provide us with a record of your visits to our Site (Collectively, the foregoing is referred to as “Usage Data”). The technology is used to gather “cookie” information that is provided by the Internet browser you use, and is stored on your computer.

#### Deleting personal information

If you would like to have your personally identifiable information removed then please contact us at [support@spacial.com](mailto:support@spacial.com) and we will use reasonable efforts to comply with your request.

#### Contact

If you have any questions regarding this policy, or your dealings with our website, please contact us here:

Spacial Audio

##### [Contact Us](https://spacial.com/contact-us/)

Contact the

Spacial Support Team

Monday – Friday  
From 4 am to 4 pm CST (UTC-6)

Mail us: [support@spacial.com](mailto:support@spacial.com)  
Web: [Contact form](https://spacial.zendesk.com/anonymous_requests/new)

##### [Products](https://spacial.com/radio-automation-software/)

##### [Help Center](https://spacial.com/help-center/)

##### [About Us](https://spacial.com/about-us/)

##### Want to hear from us?

###### Creator of leading radio automation software and other audio solutions.

###### © 2024 Triton Digital Canada Inc.

MENU MENU

SPACIAL

Subscribe to our Newsletter
---------------------------

First Name

Last Name

Email

 I agree
